Guide to the Max Wilk Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- January 2003 Acquisition, 1979-1981; 32; 2; (2 boxes)
  Boxes 47-48 contain audiovisual materials. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Contact Access Services for further information.
  - Audiocassettes
    Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - "Interviews with Audrey Wood", 1979-1981; 19 audiocassettes (Box 47)
      - Audrey Wood tape #1, 1979 March 18; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610739)
        Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - A. Wood re: Liebling, 1979 April 1; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610697)
      - A. Wood reviews the future projects, 1980 September 27; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610689)
      - A. Wood: Carson McCullers / [Truman] Capote, 1980 August 29; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610705)
      - Audrey Wood re: room service, Wm. Liebling, 1980 February 24; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610713)
      - Audrey Wood, 1979 October 21; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610721)
      - Audrey Wood personal reminiscences (Royalton Hotel), "Love Among the Ruins", 1981 January 24; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610747)
      - A. Wood re: MCA, 1980 October 20; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610754)
      - A. Wood re: Preston Jones, 1980 April 27; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610762)
      - A. Wood re: Tennessee Williams; one final speech, TW re: AW, events leading to their break-up, 1980 August 24; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610770)
      - Audrey Wood (T. Williams 1947-on); Summer + Smolce (Margo Jones), Camino Real - Rose Tattoo - [Anna] Magnani, 1980 August 21; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610788)
      - Audrey Wood, Jed Harris, 1979 June 25; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610796)
      - A. Wood, T. Williams, 1980 August 22; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610804)
      - Audrey Wood talks about Jennifer Jones and Robert Walker, undated; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610812)
      - Audrey Wood, 1980 March 30; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610820)
      - Audrey Wood, Jerome Robbins, Carson McCullers, 1979 April 9; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610838)
      - A. Wood re: Liebling actors, 1979 April 22; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610846)
      - Audrey Wood, Westport, 1979 March 25; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610853)
      - A. Wood (Liebling), 1980 November 9; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610861)
    - "Interview: Studs Terkel, re: Audrey Wood", NY, 1980 September 29; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610879)
    - "Interview: Robert Anderson, re: Audrey Wood", 1980 July 14; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610887)
    - "Interview: Arthur Kopit re: Audrey Wood", 1980 July 2; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610895)
    - "Karl Malden (Liebling), John Fearnley re: Yul Brynner, 1979 April 22-May 21; 1 (Box 47, Item barcode 39002104610903)
  - Digital audio tapes
    Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - "Interviews with Audrey Wood", 1979-1981; 7 digital audio tapes (Box 48)
      Box 48 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Dub 1, 1979 March 18-25; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002109979956)
      - Dub 2, 1979 April 1-22; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002109979964)
      - Dub 3, 1979 June 25-October 21; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002109979972)
      - Dub 4, 1980 March 30-April 27; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002109979980)
      - Dub 5, 1980 August 21-22; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002109979998)
      - Dub 6, 1980 August 24-September 27; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002109980004)
      - Dub 7, 1980 November 9 -1981 January 24; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002093778786)
    - "Interviews with Karl Malden, John Ferneley, Arthur Kopit", Dub 8, undated; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104610010)
    - "Interviews with Studs Terkel and Robert Anderson", Dub 9, 1980 July 14-September 29; 1 (Box 48, Item barcode 39002104610028)
- February 2003 Acquisition, 1993; 33; 0.21; (1 box)
  Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Contact Access Services for further information.
  - Audiocassettes
    - "Al Hirschfeld reminisces about Sweet Bye and Bye ", NY, 1993 October 21; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002109974361)
    - "Arlen, 'A Sleeping Bee'", undated; 1 (Box 49, Item barcode 39002109974379)
- May 2003 Acquisition, 1936-1991; 34; 1.42; (2 boxes)
  - Correspondence, research files, manuscripts and other papers related to Represented by Audrey Wood, 1944-1991; 16 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence, research files, manuscripts and other papers related to Represented by Audrey Wood, 1936-1982; 6 (Box 51)
- May 2004 Acquisition, 1881-2001; 35; 31.35; (48 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  Typescripts; correspondence; computer disks; printed material including playbills; audiovisual material including record albums and audio tapes, and other rmaterial relating to Wilk's writing projects.
  Box 90 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - List (empty), undated (Box 52)
  - Aspects of the Life of the Driscoll Family, undated (Box 52)
  - "The Beard", 1964; 5 (Box 52)
  - "The Bug", 1967 June (Box 52)
  - "A Dirty Mind Never Sleeps", 1967; 5 (Box 53)
  - "Eliminate the Middle Man", 1973; 4 (Box 54)
  - "Every Day's a Matinee", undated; 9 (Box 55)
  - "Get Out and Get Under", 1980; 6 (Box 56)
  - "Help! Help! Help!", 1980; 3 (Box 56)
  - "The Kissinger Noodles", 1973, undated; 4 (Box 57)
  - "The Kissinger Noodles", 1975, undated; 4 (Box 58)
  - "The Mighty Ten-Inch Screen", 1976; 3 (Box 59)
  - "The Moving Picture Boys", 1978; 4 (Box 59)
  - "My Masterpiece", 1970; 5 (Box 60)
  - "My Masterpiece", undated; 5 (Box 61)
  - "One of Our Brains is Dreaming", 1967; 4 (Box 62)
  - "Represented by Audrey Wood", 1981; 7 (Box 63)
  - "Rich is Better", 1962; 3 (Box 64)
  - The Wit and Wisdom of Hollywood, 1971 Jan 21; 2 (Box 64)
  - Correspondence, 1943-1970 (Box 64)
  - "Timon of Athens," photograph, circa 1940 (Box 64)
  - The early days of television, 1977-1984 (Box 65)
  - Gift: contracts, 1949-1986 (Box 65)
  - Reviews, 1967-1970 (Box 65)
  - "Everyday is Christmas", 1945 (Box 65)
  - Overweight flyer letters etc. - KID outline, 1963, undated (Box 65)
  - 1963, 1958-1962 (Box 65)
  - "Yosoo Melinoki!", 1993-1996 (Box 65)
  - Winters, Jonathan, 1970, undated (Box 65)
  - Wilder letter, undated (Box 65)
  - Saturday Review, 1954 September 25 (Box 65)
  - Sketches 54th Street Review, May 1949, George Axelrod, 1949, 1958 (Box 65)
  - Outlines TV (Hayward), 1977, undated (Box 65)
  - Notes TV book, 1969-1976; 2 (Box 65)
  - "Raggedy Ann" shooting script, undated (Box 65)
  - "Raggedy Ann, Jan '75 on", 1974-1975 (Box 65)
  - "Raggedy Ann," outlines, 1974-1975 (Box 65)
  - "Raggedy Ann", undated; 2 (Box 65)
  - 1975 ASCAP special - material about Berlin - Ellington - other songwriters, 1969-1973 (Box 65)
  - "Leave It To Larry", 1952-1953 (Box 66)
  - Used in everyday matinee, undated (Box 66)
  - "A Very Remarkable Woman," outline, 1951 August (Box 66)
  - Letters, documents, et al, 1961-1962 (Box 66)
  - Phyllis Jackson, 1964-1965 (Box 66)
  - Humor NBC proposal, "Our Secret Agenda," "Love is 617 Feet Long," "The Noel Coward Gala," etc., 1965-1969; 2 (Box 66)
  - "The Bocciagalapi Soccer Team", undated (Box 66)
  - 1963 items/Melina Mercouri's Greece, TV pilots in L.A., 1962-1965 (Box 66)
  - Letters, paper, deals etc. London, 1965-1966 (Box 66)
  - Songwriters correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 66)
  - "It's a Brand New World", 1970; 2 (Box 66)
  - "Mad Money", 1952, undated; 2 (Box 66)
  - "That's My Boy", undated (Box 66)
  - English letters et al, 1965-1966 (Box 66)
  - First outline "The Brain Drain", 1965 (Box 66)
  - Letter to Sam Spiegel, undated (Box 66)
  - Various English ventures, 1964-1966 (Box 66)
  - Notes: Swensen/Wilk, 1963 (Box 66)
  - Letters, 1962-1964 (Box 66)
  - "J. Winters Holiday on Ice", 1967 (Box 66)
  - Notes for novel, 1972-1973 (Box 66)
  - "Moonshot", 1964 (Box 66)
  - "War Is Heck", 1964 (Box 66)
  - "Here Come the British", 1966, undated (Box 66)
  - "That's the Ticket," by Hal Kantor and Max Wilk, 1962 (Box 66)
  - "May You Die in Ireland", 1965 April 29 (Box 66)
  - Mr. Williams and Miss Wood, notes, 1992 (Box 67)
  - "Mr. Williams and Miss Wood," script, 1989, 1992; 3 (Box 67)
  - TW/AW revised script, 1992 April (Box 67)
  - TW/AW rewrite notes, 1992 (Box 67)
  - TW/AW, 1989 November (Box 67)
  - TW/AW, 1989 June (Box 67)
  - TW/AW script revisions, 1992 October (Box 67)
  - Captions, "OK Oklahoma", 1992, undated (Box 67)
  - 2nd draft, "Oklahoma", 1992; 2 (Box 67)
  - Revised draft "OK Oklahoma", 1992; 2 (Box 67)
  - First draft "Oklahoma", undated (Box 67)
  - Original pages, 1991, undated; 3 (Box 67)
  - The 20th, 1959-1960 (Box 68)
  - "Speaking of the Benedicts," and proposed scripts, 1960 (Box 68)
  - "49th and Broadway", 1954 (Box 68)
  - "Help! Help! Help!" script from 1960 (photocopy), undated (Box 68)
  - "Miss Julia", 1961 (Box 68)
  - "What a Day," scripts, 1960s-1990s; 3 (Box 68)
  - "Hastings Retreat," scripts, 1961-1962; 2 (Box 68)
  - "The American Woman," script, 1963 April (Box 68)
  - "The Dog Who Would Not Die," script, 1958 (Box 68)
  - "Mad Money," scripts, 1956 (Box 68)
  - Undergrads scripts, 1957 (Box 68)
  - Haywood project for TV, scripts, 1958-1959 (Box 68)
  - "Help! Help! Help!" scripts, 1963-1964 (Box 68)
  - "A Bad Case of February" script, 1960 (Box 68)
  - "The Beard", undated (Box 68)
  - "The Bug" script, 1967 (Box 68)
  - Various scripts, 1964 (Box 68)
  - "See You at the Bar Mitzvah", 1963 (Box 68)
  - "McKeever and the Colonel", 1963 (Box 68)
  - Letters, etc., McKeever papers, 1964 (Box 68)
  - Notes, "The Beard", undated (Box 68)
  - Notes, 1962 (Box 68)
  - Notes, etc. Cyril Ritchard Pilot, 1963; 2 (Box 68)
  - "Penny" 1 & 2, 1962, 1964 (Box 68)
  - "Help! Help! Help!", 1963 (Box 68)
  - "You Loved Him In...", 1966 (Box 68)
  - "Never Under Any Circumstances Marry an Actor", 1967 (Box 68)
  - "The Jimmy Stewart Show", 1971; 2 (Box 69)
  - Overseas letters, 1944 (Box 69)
  - Notes - novel, 1969 (Box 69)
  - "The Staff" etc., 1969 (Box 69)
  - Ideas, 1956 (Box 69)
  - De Vincent, Sam, 1980-1990; 2 (Box 69)
  - "Get Happy", 1992; 2 (Box 69)
  - "These Are the Jokes", 1990-1992 (Box 69)
  - "Somewhere There's Music", 1989; 2 (Box 69)
  - "Westward Mr. Ho", 1991; 2 (Box 69)
  - Novel, pre-1990; 2 (Box 69)
  - "Westward Mr. Ho", 1991; 3 (Box 69)
  - Book dummy for "Sweet Bye", circa 1994 (Box 70)
  - 2 Lectures on comedy, undated (Box 70)
  - "My Masterpiece", 1980 (Box 70)
  - "Scribes and Pharisees", 1980-1982 (Box 70)
  - "Our Snatch", 1970 (Box 70)
  - Max Wilk credits, 1970-1980 (Box 70)
  - Seminar - Yale, 1981-1982 (Box 70)
  - "Look Out for Number One", 1970; 2 (Box 70)
  - "Growing is a Pain", 1981-1983 (Box 70)
  - Financial papers, 1946-1953; 2 (Box 70)
  - Broadway Applauds Lincoln Center, 1986 April 14 (Box 70)
  - "They're Playing Our Song...", 1986 (Box 70)
  - "Lilly of the Valley", 1978-1979; 2 (Box 70)
  - China trip, 1978 (Box 70)
  - "Mark Twain's...", undated (Box 70)
  - "Dragons," outlines, 1976-1977 (Box 70)
  - "Shanghai Express" (photocopies), undated (Box 70)
  - Winters, undated (Box 70)
  - "Joe College", 1978 (Box 70)
  - Personal notes, 1961, undated (Box 70)
  - Service WWII, 1943-1945 (Box 70)
  - Stage production programs, 1981-1990; 13 (Box 71)
  - Stern, Leonard, 2001 (Box 71)
  - Photographs, 1968 (Box 72)
  - Bright Lights, 1943 (Box 72)
  - Notes w/script, Rogers and Hart, 1973-1975; 2 (Box 72)
  - "Wit and Wisdom of Hollywood", 1970-1971; 8 (Box 72)
  - Harold Sack Part III, 1989-1993; 2 (Box 72)
  - Miscellaneous, 1940-2000; 2 (Box 72)
  - American Treasure Hunt, 1986 (Box 72)
  - Sketches (w/Auerbach/Axelrod) (Box 73)
  - "Every Day is Christmas", 1945; 2 (Box 73)
  - "I Love My Wife" wartime stuff, 1944 (Box 73)
  - Warner Brothers studio pieces for the publicity department, 1938, 1950 (Box 73)
  - Various contracts et al, 1943-1956; 2 (Box 73)
  - More sketches..., 1949-1950; 2 (Box 73)
  - "Close-Up," screenplay notes for film, 1947 (Box 73)
  - More sketches, 1949-1950 (Box 73)
  - "Brushoff", 1940 (Box 73)
  - Contract, 1957 (Box 73)
  - "Nature Boy", 1957 (Box 73)
  - Hayes, Peter Lind and Mary Healy, George Axelrod and Max Wilk, 1951, undated (Box 73)
  - "We Called It Music", 1947 (Box 73)
  - "Operation: Klein's", undated (Box 73)
  - "I Ask You", undated (Box 73)
  - "Morn of Plenty", undated (Box 73)
  - "Call Me a Cop", 1950 (Box 73)
  - "Reach for the Sky", 1950, undated; 2 (Box 73)
  - "Be a Clown", 1960 (Box 73)
  - "Heaven Will Protect the Working Girl", 1960 (Box 73)
  - "The Man Who Bought a Tavern", undated (Box 73)
  - "O'Dwyers Last Case", undated (Box 73)
  - "Every Uncle Needs an Aunt", 1950 (Box 73)
  - "Veni-Vidi-Video", undated (Box 73)
  - Short pieces, 1966 (Box 73)
  - "The Fast Dollar", 1951, undated (Box 73)
  - Navajo Eye Care, 1992 (Box 74)
  - "Prairie Dog Sees", undated (Box 74)
  - "Candy Is Dandy," contracts, 1993-1994 (Box 74)
  - Loesser, 1992 (Box 74)
  - Jazz - Ellington, 1943, 1994 (Box 74)
  - Releases "To Wit", 1996 (Box 74)
  - Letters "To Wit", 1995-1996 (Box 74)
  - Extra pps "To Wit", undated (Box 74)
  - Notes - WWII, 1975-1978 (Box 74)
  - "They're Playing Our Song", undated (Box 74)
  - Faulkner inventory, 1987 May 23 (Box 74)
  - Old jokes, 1994 (Box 74)
  - Edith Olive Scholarship, 1994 (Box 74)
  - Fields, Dorothy, 1994 (Box 74)
  - "To Woo", undated (Box 74)
  - Russia, 1992 (Box 74)
  - Old reviews, Max Wilk, etc., 1973-1977 (Box 74)
  - Outlines, "Westward Mr. Ho", 1989 (Box 74)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 74)
  - "War Is Heck", 1969 (Box 74)
  - "Storm Warning", 1946 (Box 74)
  - Berlin/Berggreen plagiarism, 1990 (Box 74)
  - Early TV scripts, 1950; 2 (Box 74)
  - "To Wit", 1996, undated; 4 (Box 74)
  - Our music, 1997 (Box 74)
  - "Get Happy", 1986 (Box 74)
  - 1979-80-81, 1979-1981 (Box 74)
  - Current business, 1981-1984; 2 (Box 74)
  - Ed Hartman interview, 1997 (Box 74)
  - "My Masterpiece", 1976-1978; 4 (Box 75)
  - Letterbook, 1905-1958 (Box 75)
  - Newsletters, 1957-1971 (Box 75)
  - "Waves of Laughter", 1976 (Box 75)
  - "Small Random Pieces of a Very Large Mosaic", undated (Box 75)
  - Letters AA, 1942-1995 (Box 75)
  - Letters #1A, 1936-1984 (Box 75)
  - Letters #2, 1936-1977 (Box 75)
  - Letters #3, 1940-1986 (Box 75)
  - Letters #4, 1955-1988 (Box 75)
  - Letters #5, 1951-1982 (Box 75)
  - Letters #6, 1953-1994 (Box 75)
  - Letters #7, 1955-1983 (Box 75)
  - Songwriters letters (34 Letters), 1954-2000 (Box 75)
  - 90s letters and memorabilia, 1991-2000 (Box 75)
  - Assorted extra letters, 1968-1978 (Box 75)
  - Unselected letters, 1958-1988 (Box 75)
  - Watercolor, undated (Box 75)
  - Ben Hecht clippings, 1941 (Box 75)
  - "Oklahoma!" programs, undated (Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1991 (Box 76)
  - "OK Oklahoma" contract and releases, 1991-1993 (Box 76)
  - "Oklahoma" legal (remainders) Byrd, 1993-1994 (Box 76)
  - Clearances, R & H Warner Chappell, 1992, undated (Box 76)
  - Transcript of taped interview - Agnes De Mille, undated (Box 76)
  - De Mille, Agnes - "Dance to the Piper", undated (Box 76)
  - "Oklahoma," addresses, 1991-1994 (Box 76)
  - Programs, photos, etc., 1985-1988 (Box 76)
  - Yale files, 1st Xeroxes, 1990, undated (Box 76)
  - Xeroxed photos, undated (Box 76)
  - Bambi for reference, undated (Box 76)
  - Museum of City of New York, undated (Box 76)
  - Guild files (Yale), 1991-1992 (Box 76)
  - Extra copies, photos, etc., 1944, 1991 (Box 76)
  - Unidentified list, undated (Box 76)
  - Greenstone, Al, undated (Box 76)
  - Times clipping, undated (Box 76)
  - Unidentified, 1991, undated (Box 76)
  - Transcript (books) Rodgers and Hammerstein, undated (Box 76)
  - Bios R & H, undated (Box 76)
  - Empty folder, undated (Box 76)
  - Theatre Guild histories, undated (Box 76)
  - Celeste's cook story, undated (Box 76)
  - Riggs, Lynn, undated (Box 76)
  - Hayes, Gordon, 1991, undated (Box 76)
  - Theatre Guild, undated (Box 76)
  - Wolf, Mary Hunter, undated (Box 76)
  - Wrap-up, undated (Box 76)
  - Tape, Agnes De Mille, undated (Box 76)
  - Holm, Celeste, undated (Box 76)
  - Steinbeck, Elaine, undated (Box 76)
  - Drake, Alfred, undated (Box 76)
  - Hammerstein, Bill, undated (Box 76)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 76)
  - Linn, Bambi, undated (Box 76)
  - Fearnley, 1990 March 26 (Box 76)
  - Hauff, undated (Box 76)
  - Friedlich, Kate, undated (Box 76)
  - Church, George; Mare Platt, 1990-1994 (Box 76)
  - Blackton, Jay, 1990 (Box 76)
  - Shiers, Paul and Vivien, 1991 January 9 (Box 76)
  - "Oklahoma!", undated (Box 76)
  - Prince, Hal; Sondheim, undated (Box 76)
  - White, Miles, 1991 January 31 (Box 76)
  - Transcript: Sondheim, undated (Box 76)
  - "Sound of Music," outpages, 1997, undated (Box 76)
  - "Sound of Music," Reuben Donnelly letters, 1998, undated (Box 76)
  - "Sound of Music," added pages, Lauri Peters, 1998 October 1998 (Box 76)
  - Correspondence, etc., 1997-1998 (Box 76)
  - Martin, Mary, 1998, undated (Box 76)
  - MS - "Sound of Genius", 1998, undated (Box 76)
  - "My Heart Belongs...", undated (Box 76)
  - Shulman, Susan, undated (Box 76)
  - Reviews, 1998, undated (Box 76)
  - Outpages, undated (Box 76)
  - Lehman, undated (Box 76)
  - Old programs, 1942-1958, 1996; 2 (Box 77)
  - Esquire, 1979 March 13 (Box 77)
  - "Help! Help! Help!", undated (Box 77)
  - Documents re: "A Ton of Bricks" (Bucks County 1962), 1961-1962 (Box 77)
  - "A Ton of Bricks", 1962 May (Box 77)
  - "All About Love" program; "Odd Odyssey", Greek film 1969, 1968-1969 (Box 77)
  - "A Ton of Bricks", 1962 March (Box 77)
  - "Trust Me," outline, 1994 (Box 77)
  - "The Jonathan Winters Antiques Mall", 1993 (Box 77)
  - Winters "The Mall", 1994 (Box 77)
  - "You're the Boss", 1991 (Box 77)
  - "The Midnight Frolics", 1994; 3 (Box 77)
  - Tiomkin lecture, 1999 January 31 (Box 77)
  - "Candy Is Dandy", 1993-1994 (Box 77)
  - "Get Happy", 1992 January (Box 77)
  - Sunny Side Up (Durante- Waxy G.), undated (Box 77)
  - "Leland," revised, 1997 (Box 77)
  - "Open the Door, Barney", 1996 July (Box 77)
  - Navajo plays, Tuba City, 52nd Street Players, 1993, undated; 2 (Box 77)
  - "The Seven Lively Arts...." CBS TV, 1978 (Box 77)
  - "Musical Jubilee," clippings, 1975 (Box 78)
  - "Try This On Your Piano", undated (Box 78)
  - "Get Happy", 1992 (Box 78)
  - "Black Beauty," scripts, 1973 (Box 78)
  - "Moving Picture Boys," reviews, etc..., 1978-1979 (Box 78)
  - Sheet music book, Memory Lane, London, 1973 (Box 78)
  - "The British Are Coming"; "Don't Tread on Me"; "Maxismo"; "Gold in the Hills", 1974-1975 (Box 78)
  - "Irving Berlin's America", 1973-1986 (Box 78)
  - "Moving Picture Boys" notes, reviews, etc. and unidentified photos, 1978 (Box 78)
  - "Anything for a Laugh" American Film Institute contracts, etc..., 1971-1972 (Box 78)
  - "Kissinger Noodles" preliminary notes, reviews, etc..., 1969-1974 (Box 78)
  - "Get Out and Get Under" preliminary notes, reviews, etc..., 1981-1982 (Box 78)
  - Typescripts related to television; unidentified clippings and negatives, 1956-1984 (Box 78)
  - First reading "Mr. Williams and Miss Wood", 1989 July 17 (Box 78)
  - "You Loved Him In...", 1966 October (Box 78)
  - "Water for a Chaser", 1964 (Box 78)
  - "The Brain Drain," "Drunk With Failure", 1965 (Box 78)
  - Rex Harrison and Rachel Roberts TV special, ABC, 1965, 1968 (Box 78)
  - Miscellaneous articles, 1981-1997 (Box 78)
  - Notes on Melina Mercouri: "Show My Village", 1964-1965 (Box 78)
  - "The Last Act on the Bill;" list of tapes; "Livingston and Evans, I Presume", 1998, undated (Box 78)
  - Harold Sack "American Treasure Hunt;" Variety column, 1962-1989 (Box 78)
  - "The Trembling of a Leaf;" "War Is Heck", 1943-1969 (Box 78)
  - "Don't Tread On Me", 1975 (Box 79)
  - "A Dirty Mind Never Sleeps;" "The Staff Hippy", 1969-1971 (Box 79)
  - "I Wonder Who's Kissing Me Now;" "Look Out for Number One", 1967, 1970 (Box 79)
  - "It's a Brand New World", 1970 (Box 79)
  - Research for "The Golden Age of Television", 1944-1979, undated; 2 (Box 79)
  - Railroad stock certificate, 1890 (Box 79)
  - "Feather in Your Cap," screenplay, 1982 (Box 79)
  - "The Cannon and the Nightingale", 1968-1969 (Box 79)
  - "It's Our World Too!", 1976 (Box 79)
  - Assorted writings, 1979, undated (Box 79)
  - "Oh Captain, My Captain;" "Catlin and the Indian", undated (Box 79)
  - Jonathan Winters presents "200 years of American Humor", 1975 (Box 79)
  - "Overture and Finale", 1999 (Box 79)
  - "The Kissinger Noodles" master set of galleys, 1975 (Box 79)
  - "Feather in Your Cap" original for film, 1982 (Box 79)
  - "The Wonderful World of Jonathan Winters," August 1970, NBC, undated (Box 79)
  - "The Treasure of Sarah Madri", 1976 (Box 79)
  - "The Junk Pile", 1960; 2 (Box 80)
  - "Oh Captain!" "The Rate of Exchange," "Biting the Golden Bullet," "Road Test", 1972-1976 (Box 80)
  - "A Ton of Bricks," notes and scripts, 1958-1966; 4 (Box 80)
  - Dusty Hall (J.L.), 1980 (Box 80)
  - "No More Nice Guy," screen treatment, 1980 (Box 80)
  - "Your Place or Mine", 1982 (Box 80)
  - They're Playing Our Song, 1972-1981 (Box 80)
  - "Reach for the Sky", undated (Box 80)
  - Durante - Ameche show, circa 1951 (Box 80)
  - "Snow Man", 1961 (Box 80)
  - McKeever pilot, 1961-1962 (Box 80)
  - Back-up material, "Help! Help! Help!", 1881, 1962-1964 (Box 80)
  - "Stiff Upper Lip", undated (Box 80)
  - Two articles rejected, 1964 (Box 80)
  - "Cora Crane", 1961 (Box 80)
  - "A Tidy Sum", 1957 (Box 80)
  - Day pilot - Hayward, "The First Folio," for TV, cavalry pilot, 1951 (Box 80)
  - "Three Cheers for Uncle Eddie", undated (Box 80)
  - Alternate people, 1963 (Box 80)
  - Untitled manuscript; War Department personnel placement questions, 1943, undated (Box 80)
  - "My Wife's Family", 1964 (Box 80)
  - "Impatient Husband", undated; 2 (Box 80)
  - "Hallie Flanagan", 1983, undated; 6 (Box 81)
  - Drafts and outlines, 1982 (Box 81)
  - English 1969, letters from my English agent (Box 81)
  - "Blackheart," etc... ideas for books, 1965-1967 (Box 81)
  - "The Man That Corrupted Hadleyburg", 1977 September (Box 81)
  - "The Twenty", 1967 July (Box 81)
  - "Hit the Deck", 1977, undated; 3 (Box 81)
  - Letter from Constano Cumming, re: "The Brass Section," "Cloud Seven", 1956 (Box 81)
  - Humor w/ Jay Williams, 1960 (Box 81)
  - "A Feather in Your Cap", undated (Box 81)
  - "I Wonder Who's Kissing Me Now", 1967 (Box 81)
  - Old scripts, 1948 (Box 81)
  - Federal Theater Project: Bread and Circuses (photocopy), undated (Box 81)
  - Credits: Max Wilk, 1941-1954, 1962 (Box 81)
  - More credits, 1953 (Box 81)
  - "Beef Encounter," sketch; "Alive and Kicking in NY," review, 1949-1951 (Box 81)
  - Untitled manuscript, undated (Box 81)
  - "Hasting's Retreat," a comedy for television, 1961 October (Box 81)
  - "Belle's Boy," (Herbie), 1983 (Box 82)
  - Perelman misc. reviews, 1986-1988 (Box 82)
  - "Broadway Scrapbook", undated (Box 82)
  - Armed Services editions, 1980 (Box 82)
  - Letters, 1953-1954 (Box 82)
  - Dramatists Bulletin, 1963 (Box 82)
  - Sketches "What A Day", undated (Box 82)
  - Reviews, 1980-1990 (Box 82)
  - "Statistics," a brief play, undated (Box 82)
  - "The Broadway Melody", 1992 (Box 82)
  - "Joint Return", 1982 (Box 82)
  - "The Moving Picture Boys", 1984 (Box 82)
  - "Jule Styne Concept," outline for a musical evening, 1985 (Box 82)
  - "Catlin and the Indians", 1988 (Box 82)
  - "I'll Take Manhattan," idea for a film, 1984, undated (Box 82)
  - "A Tough Act," reviews, 1986; 2 (Box 82)